Midtown Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Addition, 1932-1997, undated, Series 10:; (2.5 linear feet)
  - Oversize Printed Matter, 1973-1977, undated, 10.6:
    - The Kedettes Collection of Brilliant Canvases, undated (Reel 5438, Frame 1184-1194)
March 22-April 10, 1937 Paintings by Paul Cadmus
April 12-24, 1937 Paintings by Edith Nagler
April 19-May 3, 1937 Watercolors of Mexico by Eugenie Schein
Oct. 5-18, 1937 Vincent Spagna (Br15:527-529)
Oct. 19-Nov. 4, 1937 Paintings by Minna Citron
Nov. 5-22, 1937 Paul Mommer (Br15:533-535)
Nov. 23-Dec. 6, 1937 Paintings by Mary Hutchinson
Nov. 23-Dec. 6, 1937 Contemporary American Artists (Br15:536)
Dec. 7-20, 1937 Herbert Ferber (Br15:539-541)
Dec. 21-Jan. 3, 1938 Paintings by Alfred Kraemer
Jan. 4-17, 1938 Paintings by M. Azzi Aldrich
Feb. 8-26, 1938 Paintings and Drawings of Mexico by Doris Rosenthal
Sept. 16-Oct. 3, 1938 Paintings by Margit Varga
Nov. 21-Dec. 10, 1938 Paintings and Drawings by Zoltan Sepeshy
Dec. 8-24, 1938 Water Colors by Betty P. Parsons
Dec. 12-30, 1938 Water Colors of Bucks County by Lionel S. Reiss
Dec. 27-Jan. 14, 1939 Paintings by Jacob Getlar Smith
Jan. 17-Feb. 4, 1939 Paintings and Drawings by Isabel Bishop
Feb. 6-20, 1939 Paintings by Vincent Drennan
March 7-25, 1939 Paintings by Miron Sokole
March 27-April 15, 1939 Paintings of Mexico by Doris Rosenthal
April 17-May 6, 1939 Recent Paintings by Waldo Peirce
Sept. 26-Oct. 14, 1939 Paintings by Maurice Freedman
Oct. 17-Nov. 2, 1939 Paintings by Vincent Spagna
Nov. 3-20, 1939 Paintings by Minna Citron
Nov. 21-Dec. 9, 1939 Paintings by Frederic Taubes
Dec. 9-24, 1939 Water Colors by Betty P. Parsons
Jan. 3-20, 1940 Paintings by Emlen Etting
Feb. 20-March 9, 1940 Paintings by Paul Meltsner
March 19-April 6, 1940 Paintings and Watercolors by Bernardine Custer
Nov. 11-30, 1940 Paintings by Fletcher Martin
Dec. 2-21, 1940 Paintings by Simka Simkhovitch
Feb. 3-22, 1941 Paintings and Watercolors by Zoltan Sepeshy
March 3-22, 1941 Paintings by Doris Rosenthal
April 14-May 3, 1941 Paintings by Waldo Peirce
July 22-Aug. 22, 1941 Dealers Show American Art
Nov. 3-22, 1941 Pastels by Gladys Rockmore Davis
Nov. 25-Dec. 13, 1941 Water Colors by Betty P. Parsons
Dec. 15-Jan. 3, 1942 Paintings of the Tennessee Valley by Minna Citron
Jan. 6-24, 1942 Paintings by Jacob Getlar Smith
Jan. 26-Feb. 14, 1942 Watercolors by Zoltan Sepeshy
March 3-21, 1942 Tenth Anniversary Loan Exhibition, Works of Art by Midtown Artists Borrowed Back for this event from the Permanent Collections of Leading American Museums and Collectors
March 31-April 18, 1942 Watercolors by Waldo Peirce
April 27-May 16, 1942 Paintings by Vincent Spagna
May 18-June 6, 1942 Drawings by Isabel Bishop
Jan. 4-29, 1943 Watercolors by Jacob Getlar Smith
Feb. 8-March 6, 1943 Paintings of Mexico by Doris Rosenthal
March 5-27, 1943 Water Colors, Drawings and Prints by Contemporary American Artists at MacMurray College, courtesy of Midtown Galleries
March 29-April 17, 1943 Drawings by Minna Citron
April 19-May 15, 1943 Paintings by Gladys Rockmore Davis
May 17-June 4, 1943 Sculpture, Water Colors and Drawings by Herbert Ferber
Oct. 19-Nov. 6, 1943 Watercolors of the United States by Dong Kingman
Nov. 9-27, 1943 Ceramic Sculpture by Lilian Swann Saarinen
Nov. 23-Dec. 11, 1943 Drawings, Pastels, and Paintings by Doris Rosenthal
Jan. 25-Feb. 12, 1944 Paintings by William Thon
Feb. 5-21, 1944 Paintings by Mary E. Hutchinson
March 21-April 15, 1944 Paintings of the Ballet Backstage by Gladys Rockmore Davis
April 17-May 6, 1944 Paintings by Miron Sokole
May 9-27, 1944 Paintings by Waldo Peirce
May 29-June 17, 1944 Water Colors of the Stage Door Canteen and Other Home Front Activities by Bernardine Custer
Nov. 13-Dec. 2, 1944 Watercolors by Dong Kingman
Dec. 5-23, 1944 The Road to Paris, Gouaches by Emlen Etting
Dec. 26-Jan. 13, 1945 New York Harbor in Wartime by Julien Binford
Dec. 28-Jan. 15, 1945 Paintings by Fletcher Martin
Jan. 15-Feb. 3, 1945 Paintings, Gouaches and Drawings by Philip Guston
May 1-19, 1945 Paintings of Guatemala by Doris Rosenthal
Oct. 16-Nov. 3, 1945 Watercolors by Dong Kingman
Nov. 6-Dec., 1945 The Peirce Children Grow Up, Paintings by Waldo Peirce
Jan. 8-26, 1946 Memorial Exhibition of Paintings and Watercolors by Renee Lahm
Feb. 3, 1946 Upjohn Company Collection of Contemporary American Painting, High Museum of Art, Atlanta, Georgia
Feb. 19-March 9, 1946 Paintings by Henry Billings
April 23-May 11, 1946 Paintings by William Thon
Oct. 22-Nov. 9, 1946 Moods of Children, Paintings by Gladys Rockmore Davis
Oct. 6-26, 1946 Upjohn Collection of Contemporary American Paintings, Delaware Art Center, Wilmington, Delaware
Nov. 19-Dec. 7, 1946 Paintings and Watercolors by Zoltan Sepeshy
Feb. 2-March 1, 1947 Paintings by Isabel Bishop
Feb. 11-March 1, 1947 Paintings by Maurice Freedman
March 11-29, 1947 Watercolors by Dong Kingman
March 12-30, 1947 Recent Oil Paintings by Emlen Etting
April 1-26, 1947 15th Anniversary Exhibition, Painting and Sculpture by Members of the Midtown Group of American Artists
April 2-20, 1947 Recent Oil Paintings by Fred Nagler
April 13-26, 1947 Upjohn Collection of Contemporary American Paintings, Stockwell Memorial Library, Albion College, Albion, Michigan
April 29-May 16, 1947 Paintings by Lenard Kester
May 12-28, 1947 Upjohn Collection of Contemporary American Painting, Davenport Municipal Art Gallery, Davenport, Iowa
Sept. 2, 1947 Upjohn Collection of Contemporary American Painting, Brooks Memorial Art Gallery, Memphis, Tennessee
Oct. 5-25, 1947 Upjohn Collection of Contemporary American Painting, Illinois State Museum, Springfield, Illinois
Oct. 14-Nov. 1, 1947 Paintings by William Palmer
Dec. 8-29, 1947 Upjohn Company Collection of Contemporary American Painting, The Burpee Art Gallery, Rockford, Illinois
Jan. 27-Feb. 16, 1948 Paintings by Henry Koerner
Feb. 1, 1948 Upjohn Company Collection of Contemporary American Painting, Mulvane Art Museum, Washburn University, Topeka, Kansas
March 2-20, 1948 Watercolors by Dong Kingman
March 7-28, 1948 Upjohn Company Collection of Contemporary American Painting, Oklahoma Art Center, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma
March 22-April 3, 1948 American Art, A Multiple Exhibition arranged by The Association of Dealers in American Art, and Held in Their Galleries
April 6-24, 1948 Paintings and Gouaches by Maurice Freedman
April 11-25, 1948 Upjohn Company Collection of Contemporary American Painting, Isaac Delgado Museum of Art, New Orleans, Louisiana
May 6-23, 1948 Upjohn Company Collection of Contemporary American Painting, Dallas Health Museum, Dallas, Texas
May 11-29, 1948 Paintings and Mural Sketches by Emlen Etting
June 5-28, 1948 Upjohn Company Collection of Contemporary American Painting, William Rockhill Nelson Gallery of Arts and Mary Atkins Museum of Fine Arts, Kansas City, Missouri
July 6-29, 1948 Upjohn Company Collection of Contemporary American Painting, Kenosha Historical and Art Museum, Kenosha, Wisconsin
Oct. 5-23, 1948 Paintings by Lenard Kester
Jan. 4-22, 1949 Watercolors of Italy by William Thon
Jan. 25-Feb. 12, 1949 Paintings by Henry Koerner
Feb. 21-March 12, 1949 Paintings by Cecile Belle
March 15-April, 1949 Paintings and Drawings by Anatol Shulkin
April 5-23, 1949 Watercolors by Dong Kingman
May 3-21, 1949 Paintings by Isabel Bishop
June 3-26, 1949 Upjohn Company Collection of Contemporary American Painting, E. B. Crocker Art Gallery, Sacramento, California
Oct. 4-22, 1949 Paintings in Gouache by Fred Meyer
Oct. 25-Nov. 19, 1949 Paintings by Gladys Rockmore Davis
Nov. 22-Dec. 17, 1949 Paintings by Paul Cadmus, 1938-1949
Jan. 10-28, 1950 Non-Realistic and Objectionable Portraits of American Artists by Isabella Howland (drawings)
Jan. 31-Feb. 18, 1950 Paintings and Watercolors by Zoltan Sepeshy
Feb. 28-March 18, 1950 Drawings and Water Colors, Paris - Honolulu, by Emlen Etting
March 9-20, 1950 The Art Department of Northeast Missouri State Teachers College Presents... Contemporary American Artists, Midtown Galleries, New York City
March 21-April 15, 1950 Paintings and Gouaches by Henry Koerner
April 18-May 6, 1950 Paintings of Italy by William Thon
May 9-27, 1950 Recent Watercolors by Dong Kingman
Oct. 31-Nov. 25, 1950 Twenty-one Paintings in Casein and Ink by William C. Palmer
Nov. 28-Dec. 23, 1950 Recent Paintings by Fred Nagler
Jan. 2-29, 1951 Mobile Art Association Presents Contemporary Artists Circuited by Midtown Galleries
Feb. 6-24, 1951 Paintings by Miron Sokole
March 6-31, 1951 Paintings and Drawings by Henry Koerner
April 3-21, 1951 The Dance, Paintings and Drawings by Emlen Etting
May 1-26, 1951 10 Year Retrospective Exhibition of Watercolors by Dong Kingman
Oct. 9-27, 1951 Watercolors and Oil Paintings by William Thon
Nov. 6-Dec. 1, 1951 100 Drawings by Henry Koerner
Jan. 8-26, 1952 Oil Paintings by William Palmer
Feb. 5-25, 1952 Paintings by Maurice Freedman
Feb. 20-23, 1952 Paintings and Drawings by Doris Rosenthal Presented by Haygood Lasseter Interiors, Miami, through courtesy of Midtown Galleries, New York City
May 6-24, 1952 Paintings of the West Indies by Doris Rosenthal
June 4-28, 1952 20 Years of the Midtown Galleries, A Pictorial Survey of Twenty Years' Activity in the Promotion of Outstanding Contemporary American Art
Nov. 5-29, 1952 Paintings by Henry Koerner
March 31-April 25, 1953 Paintings of Spain by Gladys Rockmore Davis
April 28-May 23, 1953 Paintings by Cecile Belle
Oct. 20-Nov. 7, 1953 Paintings by Margit Varga
Nov. 17-Dec. 5, 1953 Paintings by Zoltan Sepeshy
Dec. 14-Jan. 9, 1954 Paintings by William Palmer
Feb. 9-27, 1954 Dong Kingman's Water Colors
April 6-May 1, 1954 Recent Paintings and Drawings by Henry Koerner
May 4-29, 1954 Watercolors by William Thon
Sept. 20, 1954 Art In Interiors
Oct. 19-Nov. 6, 1954 Paintings by Robert Vickrey
Nov. 16-Dec. 4, 1954 Recent Paintings by Emlen Etting
Dec. 7-31, 1954 Recent Paintings by William Thon
Jan. 25-Feb. 12, 1955 Paintings of Mexico by Doris Rosenthal
Feb. 23-March 19, 1955 Paintings by Henry Koerner
April 12-May 7, 1955 Paintings and Lithographs by Robert Sivard
May 10-June 4, 1955 Watercolors and Drawings by Dong Kingman
Oct. 25-Nov. 19, 1955 Paintings and Drawings by Isabel Bishop
Nov. 22-Dec. 17, 1955 Paintings by William Thon
Feb. 21-March 10, 1956 Paintings and Gouaches by Maurice Freedman
March 13-31, 1956 Paintings by Cecile Belle
April 3-21, 1956 Recent Paintings by Miron Sokole
May 8-June 2, 1956 Watercolors by Dong Kingman
Sept. 25-Oct. 17, 1956 5th Annual Exhibition, Art In Interiors
Nov. 20-Dec. 15, 1956 Paintings of Bali by Gladys Rockmore Davis
Dec. 26-Jan. 19, 1957 Paintings by Zoltan Sepeshy
Jan. 22-Feb. 16, 1957 Paintings of Mexico by Doris Rosenthal
Feb. 19-March 9, 1957 Paintings and Drawings by Emlen Etting
March 12-30, 1957 Paintings by Henry Koerner
May 7-June 8, 1957 25th Anniversary Loan Exhibition, Lent by American Museums and Collectors
Nov. 12-30, 1957 Paintings by Betty Parsons
Dec. 3-28, 1957 Paintings by William Palmer
Dec. 31-Jan. 25, 1958 Paintings by Fred Nagler
Feb. 18-March 15, 1958 Paintings by Henry Koerner
March 18-April 12, 1958 Watercolors by Dong Kingman
April 15-May 10, 1958 Paintings by William Thon
May 13-31, 1958 Paintings by Annette Bartle
Oct. 28-Nov. 15, 1958 Paintings by Robert Sivard
Nov. 18-Dec. 6, 1958 Paintings by Robert Vickrey
Jan. 27-Feb. 21, 1959 Paintings by Ernest Fiene
Feb. 24-March 14, 1959 Paintings by Jason Schoener
March 17-April 4, 1959 Paintings by Waldo Peirce
April 14-May 2, 1959 Sculpture by Raimondo Puccinelli
May 5-23, 1959 Annual Good Drawing Exhibition by Distinguished American Draughtsmen
Sept. 29-Oct. 21, 1959 Th Annual Exhibition, Art In Interiors
Nov. 17-Dec. 5, 1959 Paintings by Maurice Freedman
Dec. 8-26, 1959 Paintings by William Palmer
Jan. 5-30, 1960 Paintings by Henry Koerner
March 1-26, 1960 Paintings by Waldo Peirce
March 29-April 23, 1960 Paintings and Watercolors by William Thon
May 3-28, 1960 Paintings by Isabel Bishop
Sept. 20-Oct. 19, 1960 The Annual Exhibition, Art In Interiors
Oct. 25-Nov. 19, 1960 Paintings by Robert Vickrey
Nov. 22-Dec. 10, 1960 Paintings by Annette Bartle
Dec. 12-Jan. 6, 1960 Paintings by William Palmer
Dec. 13-Jan. 7, 1961 Paintings by Jason Schoener
Jan. 10-Feb. 4, 1961 Recent Paintings by Emlen Etting
Feb. 28-March 18, 1961 Drawings by Henry Koerner
March 21-April 15, 1961 Paintings by Zoltan Sepeshy
April 18-May 13, 1961 Watercolors by 5: William Thon, Jason Schoener, Robert Vickrey, Edward Betts, Fred Nagler
Sept. 27-Oct. 18, 1961 10th Anniversary Exhibition, Art In Interiors
Jan. 16-Feb. 3, 1962 Oh, Fearful Wonder of Man, Recent Paintings and Drawings by Henry Koerner
March 21-April 7, 1962 Barabbas
April 10-May 5, 1962 Paintings and Watercolors by Robert Vickrey
June 5-July 6, 1962 Oil Paintings and Watercolors by William Thon
Nov. 23-Dec. 15, 1962 30th Anniversary Loan Exhibition, Loans from American Museums and Collectors
Dec. 19-Jan. 5, 1963 Recent Paintings and Drawings by Henry Koerner
Jan. 8-Feb. 2, 1963 Oil Paintings, Nos. 1 through 25, Paintings of Maine, California, Greece, etc., Gouaches by Jason Schoener
March 5-30, 1963 Four Distinguished American Painters: William Thon, Robert Vickrey, Jason Schoener, Edward Betts
April 2-27, 1963 30 Years of Religious Painting by Fred Nagler
April 30-May 18, 1963 Forms in Light, 1959-1963, Recent Paintings by Henry Billings
Oct. 8-26, 1963 Recent Paintings by Annette Bartle
Oct. 29-Nov. 16, 1963 Recent Paintings by Maurice Freedman
Nov. 26-Dec. 21, 1963 Recent Paintings by William Palmer
Feb. 18-March 14, 1964 Paintings and Drawings by Siegfried Reinhardt
March 17-April 11, 1964 Paintings and Drawings by William Thon
April 21-May 9, 1964 Drawings, Watercolors, and Welded Sculpture by Nathan Cabot Hale
Oct. 6-31, 1964 Paintings of Maine by Midtown's Maine Artists (Hans Moller, Edward Betts, William Thon, Waldo Peirce, and Jason Schoener)
Nov. 10-Dec. 5, 1964 Paintings by Hans Moller
Dec. 8-26, 1964 Twenty Five Years of Drawing by Emlen Etting
Jan. 4-22, 1966 Paintings from the Greek Islands by Emlen Etting
Jan. 25-Feb. 12, 1966 Paintings of Greece by Jason Schoener
Feb. 15-March 12, 1966 Recent Paintings by Robert Sivard
March 15-April 2, 1966 Recent Paintings by Annette Bartle
April 5-30, 1966 Paintings and Watercolors by William Thon
Sept. 11-Oct. 7, 1966 Midtown Galleries Exhibition at Charleston Art Gallery, Charleston, W. Va.
Sept. 7-Oct. 22, 1966 Paintings of Maine by Midtown's Maine Artists (Hans Moller, William Thon, Edward Betts, Waldo Peirce, and Jason Schoener)
Oct. 25-Nov. 12, 1966 Flowers in Art, Paintings and Watercolors
Nov. 8-Dec. 3, 1966 Paintings by Siegfried Reinhardt
Dec. 6-31, 1966 Small Paintings by Major Artists (Isabel Bishop, Paul Cadmus, William Palmer, Robert Vickrey, Emlen Etting, Doris Rosenthal, Robert Sivard, Edward Betts, Jason Schoener, Roy Moyer, Waldo Peirce, Hans Moller, Charles Coiner, Maurice Freedman, Fred Nagler, etc.)
Jan. 4-28, 1967 Recent Paintings by Hans Moller
March 14-April 1, 1967 35th Anniversary Exhibition, A Documentary Presentation of Midtown Galleries' 35 Years of Varied Activities in Behalf of the Contemporary American Artist
April 4-29, 1967 Paintings by Isabel Bishop
May 9-June 3, 1967 Watercolors by Four Distinguished American Painters (William Thon, Hans Moller, Jason Schoener, Edward Betts)
Oct. 3-28, 1967 Recent Paintings of France by Robert Sivard
Oct. 31-Nov. 25, 1967 Recent Paintings by Roy Moyer
Nov. 28-Dec. 16, 1967 Watercolors by Four (William Thon, Edward Betts, Jason Schoener, Hans Moller)
Dec. 12-Jan. 6, 1968 Paintings by William Palmer
Jan. 7-28, 1968 Group Exhibition at the Columbus Museum of Arts and Crafts, Inc., Columbus, Ga., Courtesy of Midtown Galleries
Jan. 16-Feb. 10, 1968 Recent Paintings of the Scottish Highlands by Charles Coiner
Feb. 13-March 9, 1968 Recent Sculpture by Fred Meyer
March 1-April 6, 1968 Retrospective Selection of Drawings and Prints, Including Loans from Public and Private Collections, 1907-1968
April 9-May 4, 1968 Paintings of Ireland by William Thon
May 7-31, 1968 Sculpture, Watercolors and Drawings by Nathan Cabot Hale
Oct. 15-Nov. 9, 1968 Recent Paintings by Edward Betts
Nov 12-Dec. 7, 1968 Elections: Waldo Peirce, 1938-1968
Dec. 10, 1968-Jan. 4, 1969 Watercolors by 4 Members of the Midtown Group Noted for their Work in this Medium (William Thon, Edward Betts, Jason Schoener, Hans Moller)
Feb. 4-March 1, 1969 Paintings by Jason Schoner
April 1-26, 1969 Recent Paintings by Ethel Magafan
April 29-May 24, 1969 Paintings by Robert Vickrey
Oct. 7-Nov. 1 Hans, 1969 Watercolors by Five Distinguished American Painters (William Thon, Moller, Ethel Magafan, Jason Schoener, and Edward Betts)
Nov. 5-29, 1969 Paintings by Richard Mayhew
Dec. 2-27, 1969 Recent Paintings by William Palmer
Jan. 6-24, 1970 Exhibition of Paintings by Maurice Freedman
Feb., 1970 38th Anniversary Exhibition
March 3-28, 1970 Paintings of Mykonos, Etc. by Margit Varga
Sept. 29-Oct. 24, 1970 Watercolors and Pastels of Monhegan, Maine, by Hans Moller
Jan. 19-Feb. 13, 1971 Recent Paintings by Stephen Etnier
Feb. 16-March 13, 1971 Thirty-Ninth Anniversary Exhibition
March 16-April 10, 1971 Paintings by Richard Mayhew
April 13-May 8, 1971 Paintings by Charles Coiner
May 21-June 5, 1971 Earth, Sea and Sky: Naturescapes by Eight Artists, Squibb Gallery, Courtesy of Midtown Galleries
Sept. 28-Oct. 23, 1971 Paintings by Emlen Etting
Oct. 26-Nov. 20, 1971 Bishop, Cadmus, Vickrey*
Nov. 23-Dec. 18, 1971 Paintings by William Thon
Dec. 21-Jan. 15, 1972 Paintings by Maurice Freedman
Jan. 18-Feb. 12, 1972 Paintings of Latin America by Jason Schoener
Feb. 15-March 11, 1972 Fortieth Anniversary Exhibition (In Tribute to the Memory of Alan D. Gruskin)
March 14-April 8, 1972 Paintings of Maine and California by Edward Betts
May 9-June 3, 1972 Flowers in Art (Paintings by Waldo Peirce, William Palmer, Emlen Etting, Roy Moyer, Maurice Freedman, Hans Moller, Charles Coiner, Julien Binford, Robert Vickrey)
Oct. 24-Nov. 18, 1972 Waldo Peirce Memorial Exhibition, Paintings of the Last Two Decades
Oct. 3-21, 1972 Drawings by Eight Important Contemporary American Artists (Isabel Bishop, Paul Cadmus, Emlen Etting, Ethel Magafan, Richard Mayhew, Hans Moller, William Palmer, William Thon)
Nov. 21-Dec. 16, 1972 Paintings by Robert Vickrey
Dec. 19-Jan. 13, 1973 Religious and Figurative Paintings by Fred Nagler
March 6-31, 1973 Recent Paintings by Hans Moller
April 3-28, 1973 Paintings by Ethel Magafan
June 5-22, 1973 New Talent Festival
Oct. 2-27, 1973 Sculpture and Drawings by Nathan Cabot Hale
Oct. 30-Nov. 24, 1973 Recent Paintings of England, Scotland and Wales by Charles Coiner
Jan. 8-Feb. 2, 1974 A Selection of Drawings and Prints by Isabel Bishop
Feb. 5-March 2, 1974 42nd Anniversary Exhibition, Paintings of the Thirties
March 5-30, 1974 Paintings by Richard Mayhew
April 2-27, 1974 Flowers by Julien Binford
June 4-15, 1974 New Talent Festival
Oct. 1-26, 1974 Terra Cottas and Bronzes by Fred Meyer
Oct. 29-Nov. 23, 1974 Paintings and Prints by Robert Sivard
Nov. 26-Dec. 21, 1974 Paintings by William Palmer
Jan. 7-25, 1975 Recent Paintings by Robert Vickrey
Jan. 28-Feb. 22, 1975 Paintings and Gouaches by Jason Schoener
Feb. 25-March 22, 1975 Watercolor Paintings by William Thon
March 25-April 12, 1975 Paintings by Maurice Freedman
Oct. 6-31, 1975 Religious Paintings by Fred Nagler at Saint Peter's Gallery, New York City (in cooperation with Midtown Galleries)
Oct. 28-Nov. 22, 1975 Paintings by Emlen Etting
Dec. 23-Jan. 17, 1976 Richard Mayhew*
Jan. 20-Feb. 14, 1976 Paintings by Ethel Magafan
March 16-April 10, 1976 Paintings by Edward Betts
April 13-May 10, 1976 Selected Works by Paul Cadmus
May 11-28, 1976 American Landscapes (William Palmer, Charles Coiner, Robert Vickrey, Waldo Peirce, William Thon, Jason Schoener)
June 1-18, 1976 New Talent Festival
Sept. 28-Oct. 23, 1976 Paintings of The Hamptons by Margit Varga
Oct. 26-Nov. 20, 1976 Paintings by Stephen Etnier
Nov. 2-20, 1976 Illustrations by Isabel Bishop for "Pride and Prejudice" by Jane Austen
Nov. 23-Dec. 18, 1976 Paintings by Robert Vickrey
Dec. 28-Jan. 22, 1977 On Loan from a Private Collection, "Seven Deadly Sins" and "Subway Symphony" by Paul Cadmus
Jan. 25-Feb. 19, 1977 45th Anniversary Exhibition
Feb. 22-March 19, 1977 Paintings of Artists and Writers in Paris by Robert Sivard
March 22-April 16, 1977 Paintings and Watercolors by William Thon
April 19-May 14, 1977 Paintings by Maurice Freedman
May 17-June 4, 1977 New Talent and Guest Exhibition (Mary L. Buckley, Ruth Cobb, David Cobb Kupferman, Meyer Tannenbaum)
Nov. 1-26, 1977 Paintings by Waldo Peirce
Nov. 29-Dec. 24, 1977 Paintings by William Palmer
Feb. 28-March 25, 1978 Paintings of England, Scotland, Maine by Jason Schoener
March 28-April 22, 1978 Drawings and Serigraphs by Gregorio Prestopino
April 25-May 20, 1978 Terra Cottas and Bronzes by Fred Meyer
Oct. 31-Dec. 2, 1978 Paintings by Charles Coiner
Nov. 28-Dec. 16, 1978 Watercolors of Paris Shops, Dublin Pubs, etc. by Robert Sivard
Dec. 5-30, 1978 Drawings and Etchings by Isabel Bishop
Jan. 9-Feb. 3, 1979 The Seasons (Paintings by William Palmer, Paul Cadmus, William Thon, Hans Moller, Edward Betts, Emlen Etting, Gregorio Prestopino, Richard Mayhew, Maurice Freedman, Waldo Peirce, Jason Schoener, Charles Coiner)
Feb. 6-March 3, 1979 Recent Paintings by Stephen Etnier
Oct. 9-Nov. 3, 1979 Paintings by Maurice Freedman
Nov. 6-Dec. 1, 1979 Watercolors by Gregorio Prestopino
Dec. 4-29, 1979 Paul Cadmus, A Small Intimate Retrospective on the Occasion of His Seventy-fifth Birthday
Feb. 5-March 1, 1980 Drawings by Emlen Etting
March 4-29, 1980 Paintings of Summer in Maine by Jason Schoener
April 29-May 24, 1980 Paintings by Bruce Currie
Nov. 4-29, 1980 Paintings by Stephen Etnier
Dec. 2-Jan. 3, 1981 Paintings by William Thon
Jan. 6-31, 1981 Paintings by Ethel Magafan
Feb. 3-28, 1981 Watercolors by Ruth Cobb
March 3-28, 1981 Paintings by Robert Sivard
Sept. 8-Oct. 3, 1981 Self Portraits *
Oct. 6-31, 1981 A Fifty Year Drawing Retrospective and Recent Paintings by Isabel Bishop
Dec. 1-Jan. 9, 1982 William Palmer: Painting 50 Years
Jan. 19-Feb. 27, 1982 Retrospective Exhibition of Selected Paintings, 1932-1982, by Maurice Freedman
March 2-27, 1982 Retrospective Exhibition by Margit Varga
March 30-April 24, 1982 Midtown Galleries Golden Anniversary, Selected Work by Gallery Artists
April 27-May 22, 1982 New Bronzes and Terra Cottas by Fred Meyer
Oct. 5-20, 1982 Ruth Cobb: A Selection of Watercolors *
Nov. 2-27, 1982 A Twenty Year Retrospective Exhibition by Edward Betts
Jan. 4-29, 1983 Recent Paintings and Sculpture by Artists Associated with Midtown Galleries since the Thirties and Forties *
Feb. 1-26, 1983 Isabel Bishop: An Intimate Exhibition of Work of the Past Five Years
July 10-Aug. 4, 1983 Selected Works of Contemporary American Artists from the Midtown Galleries, New York City [at Fairfield University] *
Oct. 4-30, 1983 Paintings, Drawings and Prints by Bernarda Bryson Shahn
Nov. 1-26, 1983 Jason Schoener: The Artist's Travels *
Nov. 29-Dec. 31, 1983 Paul Cadmus: Drawings, Prints, Photographs, 1924-1983 *
Jan. 10-Feb. 4, 1984 Emlen Etting: 50 Years of Paintings and Drawings *
Feb. 7-March 3, 1984 Ethel Magafan: Oils and Watercolors *
April 10-May 5, 1984 Charles Coiner *
Dec. 10, 1985-Jan. 8, 1986 Three Figurative Artists: Paul Cadmus, Isabel Bishop, Bernarda Bryson Shahn *
May 6-June 8, 1986 William Palmer: The Early Years, 1926-1940 *
Dec. 9, 1986-Jan. 17, 1987 Isabel Bishop: Early Drawings *
June 7-July 7, 1987 Julien Binford: Fifty Years of Painting *
Dec. 8, 1987-Jan. 31, 1988 Paul Cadmus: 50th Anniversary Exhibition *
March 2-April 9, 1988 Painting America: Mural Art in the New Deal Era (in association with Janet Marqusee Fine Arts) *
Nov. 11-Dec. 30, 1989 Walt Kuhn *
Feb. 22-April 7, 1990 Close Encounters: The Art of Paul Cadmus, Jared French, and George Tooker *